Barbara B. Kennelly Papers
© 2004 University of Connecticut
- Series V: Subject Files, 1978-1998
  - Subseries H: 103rd Congress, 1993-1994
    - Low Income Energy Assistance Program (LIHEAP) - 103rd Congress, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 25)
    - Microenterprise, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 26)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 27)
    - National Service, 1992-1993 (Box 29:, Folder 28)
    - National Service - Clinton Proposal, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 29)
    - National Service Act, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 30)
    - National Service Act - Ammendments, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 31)
    - Pratt and Whitney - Agreement with International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAMAW), 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 32)
    - Pratt and Whitney - F-15 Engine Conract, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 33)
    - Pratt and Whitney - Joint Training Partnership Act (JTPA) Grant, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 34)
    - Pratt and Whitney - Restructuring Details, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 35)
    - Press Contacts, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 36)
    - Romania - Most Favored Nation, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 37)
    - Tax - Camp Counselors, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 38)
    - Tax - Police / Firefighters Tax Clarification, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 39)
    - The Higher Education Savings Act of 1993 (Box 30:, Folder 1-2)
    - Timex 103rd (GSP), 1993 (Box 30:, Folder 3)
    - Trade - China - Footwear, 1993 (Box 30:, Folder 4)
    - Trade - China - Most Favored Nation (MFN), 1993 (Box 30:, Folder 5)
    - Trade - China - Most Favored Nation (MFN) (Industry Papers), 1993 (Box 30:, Folder 6)
    - Trade - Customs, 1993 (Box 30:, Folder 7-8)
    - Trade - Hearing, 1993 (Box 30:, Folder 9)
    - Trade - Markup - Romania, APEC, NAFTA, 1993 (Box 30:, Folder 10)
    - Trade - NAFTA - Floor, 1993 (Box 30:, Folder 11)
    - Trade - NAFTA - Full Committee, 1993 (Box 30:, Folder 12)
    - Trade - NAFTA - Full Committee Vote, 1993 (Box 30:, Folder 13)
    - Trade - NAFTA - Full Committee Walk-through of NAFTA, 1993 (Box 30:, Folder 14)
    - Trade - NAFTA - Hearing, 1993 (Box 30:, Folder 15-16)
    - Trade Adjustment Assistance, 1993 (Box 30:, Folder 17)
    - Univerity of Hartford - Commencement, 1993 (Box 30:, Folder 18)
    - Ways and Means - Committee Markup, 1993 (Box 30:, Folder 19)
    - Ways and Means - Debt Ceiling, 1993 (Box 30:, Folder 20)
    - Ways and Means - Health Care - Highlights of the President's Health Plan and the Cooper and Chafee Health Plans, 1993 (Box 30:, Folder 21-22)
    - Ways and Means - Health Care - President Clinton's Health Care Reform Proposal - Draft, 1993 (Box 31:, Folder 1-2)
    - Ways and Means - Health Care - Presidents Health Plan Memo, 1993 (Box 31:, Folder 3)
    - Ways and Means - Health Care, 1993 (Box 31:, Folder 4-9)
    - Ways and Means - Health Care Financing, 1993 (Box 31:, Folder 10)
    - Women's Specialty Retailing Group (WSRG) - Trade Speech - Enfield, CT, 1993 (Box 31:, Folder 11)
    - Xerox - Duties / Tarriffs, 1993 (Box 31:, Folder 12)
    - Yale Trade Problem, 1993 (Box 31:, Folder 13)
    - Aerospace and GATT, 1994 (Box 31:, Folder 14)
    - Aerospace Language, 1994 (Box 31:, Folder 15)
    - Bridgeport Courthouse, 1994 (Box 31:, Folder 16)
    - Children's Hospital, 1994 (Box 31:, Folder 17)
    - Circulated Announcements, 1994 (Box 31:, Folder 18)
    - Cosponsorships 103rd Congress 2nd Session, 1994 (Box 31:, Folder 19)
    - Crime: Colt M4, 1994 (Box 31:, Folder 20)
    - Defense - C 17 Airlift for FY 95, 1994 (Box 31:, Folder 21)
    - Defense - Seawolf - Strategy, 1994 (Box 31:, Folder 22)
    - Education: EAI, 1994 (Box 31:, Folder 23)
    - EITC Bill, 1994 (Box 31:, Folder 24)
    - Employee Retirement Income Security Act (ERISA), 1994 (Box 31:, Folder 25)
    - Entitlements, 1994 (Box 31:, Folder 26)
    - Environment - Connecticut Interior Appropriations, 1994 (Box 32:, Folder 1)
    - Haiti, 1994 (Box 32:, Folder 2)
    - Health - Mark-up, 1994 (Box 32:, Folder 3)
    - Health, 1993-1994 (Box 32:, Folder 4-6)
    - Health Care - An Analyisis of the Administrations Health Proposal, 1994 (Box 32:, Folder 7)
    - Health Care - An Analysis of Congressman Gephart's Health Proposal, 1994 (Box 32:, Folder 8)
    - Health Care - An Analysis of Managed Competition Act, 1994 (Box 32:, Folder 9)
    - Health Care - Connecticut Conference of Municipalities (CCM) Problem, 1994 (Box 32:, Folder 10)
    - Health Care - Democratic Cauxcus Health Care Reform Proposal, 1994 (Box 32:, Folder 11)
    - Health Care - Kennelly Priorities, 1994 (Box 32:, Folder 12)
    - Health Care - Mark-up - Mitchell Summary, 1994 (Box 32:, Folder 13)
    - Health Care - Ways and Means Markup, 1994 (Box 32:, Folder 14-18)
    - Health Care Reform - Chairman's Mark - Ways and Means, 1994 (Box 32:, Folder 19)
    - Health Care Reform - Gephart Bill, 1994 (Box 32:, Folder 20)
    - Health Care Reform - Price/Cost Controls, 1994 (Box 32:, Folder 21)
    - Health Memos, 1993-1994 (Box 33:, Folder 1-3)
    - Health Security Act - Impact for Connecticut, 1994 (Box 33:, Folder 4)
    - Health Security Act - Section by Section Analysis, 1993-1994 (Box 33:, Folder 5)
    - Insurance Reform, 1994 (Box 33:, Folder 6)
    - Insurance Reform - BBK Anti-Cost Shifting Amendment, 1994 (Box 33:, Folder 7)
    - ISTEA Regulations, 1994 (Box 33:, Folder 8)
    - Lead Screening Bill, 1994 (Box 33:, Folder 9)
    - Leadership: Vice Chair Race, 1994 (Box 33:, Folder 10)
    - Life Insurance - Taxation, 1992-1994 (Box 33:, Folder 11)
    - Long Term Care Act of 1994 (Box 33:, Folder 12)
    - Long-term Care, 1994 (Box 33:, Folder 13)
    - Long-term Care - AARP, 1994 (Box 33:, Folder 14)
    - Long-term Care Draft, 1994 (Box 33:, Folder 15)
    - Micro-Enterprise FAA, 1994 (Box 33:, Folder 16)
    - Newington Veterans Medical Center, 1994 (Box 33:, Folder 17)
    - Pension: BBK Bill, 1994 (Box 33:, Folder 18)
    - PPS Exempt / Rehabilitation Hospitals, 1994 (Box 33:, Folder 19-20)
    - Prosecuter, 1994 (Box 33:, Folder 21)
    - Questionnaire - United Auto Workers (UAW), 1994 (Box 33:, Folder 22)
    - Questionnaires, 1994 (Box 33:, Folder 23-24)
    - Social Security: Nanny Tax / Independent Agency, 1994 (Box 33:, Folder 25-26)
    - Special Olympics Duty, 1994 (Box 33:, Folder 27)
  - Subseries I: 104th Congress, 1995-1996
    - 76th Division/104th Congress, 1995 (Box 34:, Folder 1)
    - Accelerated Death Benefit (ABDs), 1995 (Box 34:, Folder 2-3)
    - Blind Amendment, 1995 (Box 34:, Folder 4)
    - Blind Vendors, 1995 (Box 34:, Folder 5)
    - Budget - Balenced Budget Act of 1995 (Box 34:, Folder 6-8)
    - C-17 104th Congress, 1995 (Box 34:, Folder 9)
    - Charter Oak, 1995 (Box 34:, Folder 10)
    - Child Maltreatment, 1995 (Box 34:, Folder 11)
    - Child Support 15% Fee, 1995 (Box 34:, Folder 12-13)
    - Child Support Bill, 1995 (Box 34:, Folder 14-15)
    - Child Support: 15% Fee Hearing, 1995 (Box 34:, Folder 16)
    - Children - Improving Court Practice in Child Abuse and Neglect Cases, 1995 (Box 34:, Folder 17)
    - Community Food, 1995 (Box 34:, Folder 18)
    - Connecticut Welfare, 1995 (Box 34:, Folder 19-20)
    - CT Basketball NCAA Women's Final Four, 1995 (Box 34:, Folder 21)
    - Debt Ceiling, 1995 (Box 35:, Folder 1-5)
    - Department of Defense (DOD) Authorization Statements, 1995 (Box 35:, Folder 6)
    - EITC, 1995 (Box 35:, Folder 7-12)
    - EITC - Hearing, 1995 (Box 35:, Folder 13-14)
    - EITC - Hearing of the Committee on Ways and Means, 1995 (Box 35:, Folder 15-17)
    - Family Preservation Hearing, 1995 (Box 35:, Folder 18)
    - Financial Institution and Real Estate Relief Act (Fire) 105th Congress, 1995 (Box 35:, Folder 19)
    - Foreign Aid - Abortion / Family Planning, 1995 (Box 35:, Folder 20)
    - Fuel Cells, 1995 (Box 35:, Folder 21)
    - Gephart Medicare, 1995 (Box 35:, Folder 22)
    - Griffen Line: Major Investment Study, 1995 (Box 35:, Folder 23)
    - Health Care Reform - Health Insurance Association of America, 1995 (Box 35:, Folder 24)
    - Healthcare Task Force, 1995 (Box 35:, Folder 25)
    - Insurers and Medicare Reform, 1995 (Box 35:, Folder 26)
    - Medicare - Health Ambulance Amendment, 1992-1995 (Box 36:, Folder 1-2)
    - Medicare Alternative Hearing, 1995 (Box 36:, Folder 3)
    - Medicare Hearing, 1995 (Box 36:, Folder 4-7)
    - Medicare Reform - House Floor, 1995 (Box 36:, Folder 8-11)
    - Medicare Reform - Ways and Means Summary, 1995 (Box 36:, Folder 12-13)
    - Medicare Reform Hearings, 1995 (Box 36:, Folder 14)
    - National Center for Policy Analysis, 1995 (Box 36:, Folder 15)
    - Pension Bill, 1995 (Box 36:, Folder 16)
    - Rapid Deployment Strike Force Act - HR 97, 1995 (Box 36:, Folder 17)
    - Romania - Amnesty International Report, 1995 (Box 36:, Folder 18)
    - Romania - MFN Status, 1995 (Box 36:, Folder 19)
    - Route 6 Expressway, 1995 (Box 36:, Folder 20-21)
    - Route 6 Expressway (Cont'd.), 1995 (Box 37:, Folder 1-2)
    - Smith International Family Planning Amendment - HR 1561, 1995 (Box 37:, Folder 3)
    - Social Security, 1995 (Box 37:, Folder 4-5)
    - Social Security - Administration, 1995 (Box 37:, Folder 6)
    - Social Security - Disability, 1995 (Box 37:, Folder 7)
    - Social Security - Disability Hearings, 1995 (Box 37:, Folder 8)
    - Social Security Earnings Test, 1995 (Box 37:, Folder 9-10)
    - Tax - Police and Fire / Connecticut, 1995 (Box 37:, Folder 11)
    - Tax Revenue Estimation, 1990-1995 (Box 37:, Folder 12)
    - Thomas Health Bills, 1995 (Box 37:, Folder 13)
    - Timex - GSP Language, 1995 (Box 37:, Folder 14)
    - Trade - The White House Conference for Trade and Investment in Ireland, 1995 (Box 37:, Folder 15)
    - Trinity College, 1995 (Box 37:, Folder 16)
    - Village for Families and Children, 1995 (Box 37:, Folder 17)
    - Violence Against Women Act, 1995 (Box 37:, Folder 18)
    - Ways and Means: Medicare Aendments, 1995 (Box 37:, Folder 19-22)
    - Welfare Reform Task Force, 1994-1995 (Box 37:, Folder 23)
    - Women's Health - [Info, Letters], 1995 (Box 37:, Folder 24)
    - Women's Issues - United Nations Fourth World Conference on Women - Beijing, China, 1995 (Box 37:, Folder 25)
    - 104th Congress Issues: Budget Background, 1996 (Box 38:, Folder 1)
    - 104th Congress Issues: Campaign Finance Reform / Crime / Misc., 1996 (Box 38:, Folder 2)
    - 104th Congress Issues: Connecticut Data, 1994-1996 (Box 38:, Folder 3)
    - 104th Congress Issues: Dole / Economy / Contract, 1996 (Box 38:, Folder 4)
    - 104th Congress Issues: Environment / Tax, 1996 (Box 38:, Folder 5)
    - 104th Congress Issues: Labor / Defense / Trade / Anti-terrorism / Death Penalty / Housing, 1996 (Box 38:, Folder 6)
    - 104th Congress Issues: Medicare / Welfare, 1996 (Box 38:, Folder 7)
    - 104th Congress Issues: Minimum Wage / Debt Ceiling, 1996 (Box 38:, Folder 8)
    - ABB, 1996 (Box 38:, Folder 9)
    - Adoption, 1994-1996 (Box 38:, Folder 10)
    - Adoption "Reasonable Efforts", 1996 (Box 38:, Folder 11)
    - AETNA / Travelers - Connecticut Job Loss, 1996 (Box 38:, Folder 12)
    - AIDS/HIV, 1996 (Box 38:, Folder 13)
    - Child Support and Telephones, 1996 (Box 38:, Folder 14)
    - Child Support Implementation Hearing, 1996 (Box 38:, Folder 15-17)
    - China-U.S. Relations in a Post Cold War World Information Pack, 1996 (Box 38:, Folder 18)
    - China-U.S. Relations, MFN Status, and Economic Conditions Information Pack, 1996 (Box 38:, Folder 19)
    - Church Fires, 1996 (Box 38:, Folder 20)
    - Clinton Convention DNC, 1988-1996 (Box 38:, Folder 21)
    - Colt, 1996 (Box 38:, Folder 22)
    - CPI, 1996 (Box 38:, Folder 23-24)
    - Connecticut Childrens Hospital, 1996 (Box 38:, Folder 25)
    - Debt Ceiling - Treasury Letters, 1995-1996 (Box 38:, Folder 26)
    - Defense, 1993-1996 (Box 38:, Folder 27)
    - Democratic Caucus Material, 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 1-3)
    - Democratic Caucus: Economic Renewal Task Force Reports, 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 4)
    - Democratic Convention, 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 5-6)
    - DNC, 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 7)
    - EITC, 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 8)
    - EITC - Background - Dept. of Treasury, 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 9)
    - EITC - Memos, 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 10)
    - EITC - Senate Proposals, 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 11)
    - EITC - Tax, 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 12)
    - EITC - Treasury, 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 13)
    - False Bomb Threat Penalty Act, 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 14)
    - Families First Agenda and Women, 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 15)
    - Federal Locality Pay, 1993-1996 (Box 39:, Folder 16)
    - Finacial Institution and Real Estate (FIRE) Enterprise Zones, 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 17)
    - Frequent Flier Tax, 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 18)
    - Gas Tax - 104th Congress, 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 19)
    - Griffen Line, 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 20-23)
    - Hartford Housing Welfare, 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 24)
    - Hartford Whalers, 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 25)
    - Health Care - OBGYN, 1994-1996 (Box 39:, Folder 26)
    - Health Care Reform - Mutual of Omaha, 1993-1996 (Box 39:, Folder 27)
    - Hot Section Letter Released by White House, 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 28)
    - Hot Sections - UTC, 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 29)
    - Housing, 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 30)
    - Housing Oppurtunities for People With AIDS (HOPWA), 1996 (Box 39:, Folder 31)
    - Ireland/U.S. Materials, 1996 (Box 40:, Folder 1)
    - Ireland/U.S. Public Leadership, 1996 (Box 40:, Folder 2)
    - Irish Affairs - Lawlor, 1995-1996 (Box 40:, Folder 3)
    - Irish-American Community Rally, 1996 (Box 40:, Folder 4)
    - Kansas City Platform, 1996 (Box 40:, Folder 5)
    - LIHEAP, 1996 (Box 40:, Folder 6)
    - Long Term Care (LTC) - Tax Clarifications, 1996 (Box 40:, Folder 7-8)
    - Longterm Care Reserves, 1996 (Box 40:, Folder 9)
    - Medicare Technicals, 1994-1996 (Box 40:, Folder 10)
    - Medicare Trust Fund Hearing, 1996 (Box 40:, Folder 11)
    - Memorial Day, 1996 (Box 40:, Folder 12)
    - Minimum Wage, 1996 (Box 40:, Folder 13)
    - NE Utilities Millstone, 1996 (Box 40:, Folder 14)
    - Northern Ireland, 1995-1996 (Box 40:, Folder 15-16)
    - Old State House Rededication, 1996 (Box 40:, Folder 17)
    - Partnership for Long-term Care, 1996 (Box 40:, Folder 18-24)
    - Pension Reform - Heart/Hypertension, 1996 (Box 41:, Folder 1)
    - Phoenix Tax, 1995-1996 (Box 41:, Folder 2-3)
    - Pittsburgh Platform, 1996 (Box 41:, Folder 4)
    - Public Debt Ceiling Materials, 1995-1996 (Box 41:, Folder 5-8)
    - Questionnaires, 1995-1996 (Box 41:, Folder 9-12)
    - Roll Call Letter, 1996 (Box 41:, Folder 13)
    - Romania - MFN, 1996 (Box 41:, Folder 14)
    - Route 6 Project - EPA meeting, 1996 (Box 41:, Folder 15)
    - Science Center, 1996 (Box 41:, Folder 16)
    - Smart Gun, 1996 (Box 41:, Folder 17)
    - Social Security Earnings Test, 1996 (Box 41:, Folder 18)
    - Social Security Technical Amendments - HR 4039, 1996 (Box 41:, Folder 19)
    - Social Security: Background, 1996 (Box 41:, Folder 20)
    - Social Security: Private 1996 CBO / Mtg (Box 41:, Folder 21)
    - Special Order on Women Wages, and Jobs, 1996 (Box 41:, Folder 22)
    - State House Commemorative Coin, 1996 (Box 41:, Folder 23)
    - Talking Points, 1996 (Box 41:, Folder 24)
    - Title X Family Planning / Abortion, 1996 (Box 41:, Folder 25)
    - US Surgical Breast Biopsy Device - FDA, 1996 (Box 41:, Folder 26)
    - UTC - China, 1996 (Box 41:, Folder 27)
    - UTC - Export Controls, 1996 (Box 41:, Folder 28)
    - Ways and Means: Health Insurance Markup, 1996 (Box 42:, Folder 1-4)
  - Subseries J: 105th Congress, 1997-1998
    - Adoption - Background, 1997 (Box 42:, Folder 5-9)
    - Adoption - Foster Care Hearing, 1997 (Box 42:, Folder 10)
    - Adoption - Hearing on Kennelly Adoption Bill, 1997 (Box 42:, Folder 11)
    - Adoption - Senate Adoption Bill, 1997 (Box 42:, Folder 12-13)
    - Adoption, 1997 (Box 42:, Folder 14-15)
    - Adoption Bill - Press, 1997 (Box 42:, Folder 16)
    - Adoption Resolution 105th Congress, 1997 (Box 42:, Folder 17)
    - Adoption Resolution: Discussion Draft 105th Congress, 1997 (Box 42:, Folder 18)
    - Assets in Liquidation, 1997 (Box 42:, Folder 19)
    - Bills, 1997 (Box 42:, Folder 20-21)
    - Chandler Evans, 1997 (Box 42:, Folder 22)
    - Charter Oak, 1997 (Box 42:, Folder 23)
    - Child Abuse and Neglect: A Look at the States, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 1)
    - Child IRA's, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 2)
    - CIGNA / Japan / USTR, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 3)
    - Commerce, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 4)
    - Connecticut Jobs First, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 5)
    - Connecticut Welfare Waiver, 1995-1997 (Box 43:, Folder 6)
    - Connecticut Charter Schools, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 7)
    - Connecticut River - American Heritage River, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 8)
    - DCCC Dinner, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 9)
    - Defense, 1995-1997 (Box 43:, Folder 10)
    - Department of Transportation & Related Industries Appropriations Bill, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 11)
    - EITC, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 12)
    - EITC - Hearing before the Committee on Ways and Means, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 13)
    - EITC - Welfare Markup, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 14)
    - FAA Repair Stations, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 15)
    - Faith St. Claire, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 16)
    - Fannie May, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 17)
    - Firearms, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 18)
    - Foster Care - The State of Children, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 19)
    - Government Pension Offset, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 20)
    - Hartford Schools, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 21)
    - Health Care - Families First / Kids Only Health Policies, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 22-24)
    - Health Care - Insurance Coverage for Emergency Care, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 25)
    - Historic Preservation, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 26)
    - House Adoption Reform Legislation, 1997 (Box 43:, Folder 27)
    - ISTEA, 1996-1997 (Box 44:, Folder 1)
    - ISTEA: 6 Month Extension, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 2)
    - ISTEA: BESTEA/ISTEA General Info, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 3)
    - ISTEA: Clips, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 4)
    - ISTEA: Connecticut, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 5)
    - ISTEA: Kennelly's Projects, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 6)
    - ISTEA: Letters NGA, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 7)
    - ISTEA: Lott Letter, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 8)
    - ISTEA: Memos, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 9-10)
    - ISTEA: Welfare to Work, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 11)
    - Kennelly CBO Marriage Penalty, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 12)
    - Kolbe Codel - China, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 13-14)
    - Kolbe Codel Itinerary, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 15)
    - Kolbe Codel to do Prep, 1996-1997 (Box 44:, Folder 16)
    - Life/Nonlife Consolodation, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 17)
    - Mammography / Medicare / BBK Bill, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 18)
    - Military - Non-Conforming Parts, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 19)
    - Overview and Summary of the Mission (Trip to Hong Kong and China), 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 20)
    - Pensions, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 21)
    - Pfizer / China Price Control, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 22)
    - Questionnaire - Hartford Courant, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 23)
    - Reconciliation - Trade, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 24)
    - Retirement Coverage Material, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 25)
    - Roland / Kids Health, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 26-28)
    - ROTC, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 29)
    - Social Security - Acquiescence / SSA Regulation, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 30)
    - Social Security - Advisory Council on Social Security - 3 Plans, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 31)
    - Social Security - COCA / CPI, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 32)
    - Social Security - Cycling Payments, 1997 (Box 44:, Folder 33)
    - Social Security - Disability, 1997 (Box 45:, Folder 1-2)
    - Social Security - Disability Hearings, 1997 (Box 45:, Folder 3-4)
    - Social Security - Great Social Security Tax Information, 1997 (Box 45:, Folder 5)
    - Social Security - Hearing - CRS / GAO, 1997 (Box 45:, Folder 6)
    - Social Security - Hearing - Members, 1997 (Box 45:, Folder 7)
    - Social Security - Hearing, 1997 (Box 45:, Folder 8-9)
    - Social Security - Internet, 1997 (Box 45:, Folder 10)
    - Social Security - Privatization Hearing, 1997 (Box 45:, Folder 11-13)
    - Social Security - Privatized, 1997 (Box 45:, Folder 14-15)
    - Social Security - Public Earnings and Benefit Estimate Statements (PEBES)- Internet, 1997 (Box 45:, Folder 16)
    - Social Security - Public Earnings and Benefit Estimate Statements on Internet - Hearings, 1997 (Box 45:, Folder 17)
    - Social Security - Suspense File, 1997 (Box 45:, Folder 18)
    - Social Security - Womens Retirement Income, 1997 (Box 45:, Folder 19)
    - Social Security Advisory Council Hearing, 1997 (Box 45:, Folder 20)
    - Social Security and Workers Compensation, 1997 (Box 45:, Folder 21)
    - Stowe Village, 1997 (Box 45:, Folder 22)
    - Tax - HR2510 - 100% Consolodation, 1997 (Box 45:, Folder 23)
    - Tax Reform - Police/Fire Administration and Implementation, 1997 (Box 45:, Folder 24)
    - The Patient Access to Responsible Care Act of 1997 (Box 46:, Folder 1)
    - Trade - ABB Tarriff, 1997 (Box 46:, Folder 2)
    - Trade - Export / Import Bank, 1997 (Box 46:, Folder 3)
    - Trade - Fast Track, 1997 (Box 46:, Folder 4)
    - Trade - KODAK Film Dispute, 1997 (Box 46:, Folder 5)
    - Transition to Work Act, 1997 (Box 46:, Folder 6-8)
    - Transportation - Aviation - All Testimony, 1997 (Box 46:, Folder 9)
    - Trinity, 1997 (Box 46:, Folder 10)
    - Ways and Means Markup, 1997 (Box 46:, Folder 11)
    - Ways and Means - Medicare Markup, 1997 (Box 46:, Folder 12-18)
    - Ways and Means - Welfare Markup, 1997 (Box 46:, Folder 19-20)
    - Ways and Means - Welfare Markup (Cont'd.), 1997 (Box 47:, Folder 1-2)
    - Woman's Leadership Forum, 1997 (Box 47:, Folder 3)
    - Accomplishments for Congress, 1998 (Box 47:, Folder 4)
    - AED's on Airlines, 1997-1998 (Box 47:, Folder 5)
    - Agriculture, 1998 (Box 47:, Folder 6)
    - American Association of University Women, 1998 (Box 47:, Folder 7)
    - Animal Rights, 1998 (Box 47:, Folder 8)
    - Arts, 1998 (Box 47:, Folder 9)
    - BESTA, 1998 (Box 47:, Folder 10)
    - Budget, 1998 (Box 47:, Folder 11-12)
    - Campaign Finance Reform (CFR) Task Force Meetings, 1997-1998 (Box 47:, Folder 13)
    - Child Care, 1998 (Box 47:, Folder 14-15)
    - Connecticut Child Care, 1997-1998 (Box 47:, Folder 16)
    - CRS Reports For Congress, 1997-1998 (Box 47:, Folder 17)
    - CRS Reports for Congress, 1998 August (Box 47:, Folder 18)
    - Defense, 1998 (Box 47:, Folder 19)
    - Democratic Caucus: Issues Conference, 1998 (Box 47:, Folder 20-21)
    - DWI, 1998 (Box 47:, Folder 22)
    - Education, 1997-1998 (Box 47:, Folder 23)
    - Environment, 1998 (Box 47:, Folder 24)
    - Fairfield University Distance Learning, 1998 (Box 47:, Folder 25)
    - General ISTEA Info, 1998 (Box 47:, Folder 26)
    - Government Reform, 1998 (Box 47:, Folder 27)
    - Grasso Stamp, 1998 (Box 47:, Folder 28)
    - Health, 1998 (Box 47:, Folder 29)
    - Health / Bill of Rights: Health INS Regulation, 1998 (Box 47:, Folder 30)
    - Health / Bill of Rights: Health INS Regulation (Cont'd.), 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 1-5)
    - Health Care, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 5)
    - Health Care - Amending Health Care: 105th Congress, 2nd Session, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 6)
    - Health Care - Providing New Patient Protections: 105th Congress, 2nd Session, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 7)
    - Housing, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 8)
    - ISTEA, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 9)
    - ISTEA: Conn DOT - Impact of Failure to Pass ISTEA, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 10)
    - ISTEA: HR2400 State Info, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 11)
    - ISTEA: Kennelly's notes on Rep. Oberstar, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 12)
    - ISTEA: Pro/Con Divisions, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 13)
    - ISTEA: Projects, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 14)
    - Labor, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 15)
    - Marriage Tax Information, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 16)
    - Medicaid Breast Cancer Coverage and CDC Screening, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 17)
    - Medicare / Medicaid Rowland, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 18)